animenetzone.com 2013-01-31

# Privacy Policy | Dubbed Anime

### Introduction

Dubbed Anime is committed to protecting your privacy to allow for a safe and secure experience. This privacy policy outlines how information is collected and used. As our content and services constantly evolve we may modify this policy from time to time.

### Information Collection

We may collect information from you in order for you to use our services. This can include, but is not limited to your name, email address, and Internet Protocol address. Aside from your name or chosen nickname, other information will not be publicly available to others. We do not promote nor send spam thus we will not redistribute your information to any third parties.

We may collect cookies from your computer depending on your preferences. Cookies are plain text files that are stored on your computer generally used to serve to your convenience for future visits. This can prevent repeatedly performing tasks such as typing in your name or email address each time by saving this information for future use. You can stop accepting cookies by configuring the settings in your browser, however, you may not be able to fully use the website features.

In addition, third party advertisements may also set and/or read cookies on your computer to collect information about users who view or interact with their advertisements. The general use of this information is for the purpose of reporting website traffic, statistics, advertisement click-throughs, and other activities on the website by using cookies, web beacons, and other monitoring technologies to compile anonymous statistics about our website visitors. No personally identifiable information is collected by or transferred to any party other than the Advertiser. The actions of such parties and how they use such information is subject to the particular third party’s privacy policy. To opt out from such information collection please visit the following link: http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.

### Obligation to Children’s Privacy

We never collect or maintain information from those who we actually know are under 13 years of age. Such information will be deleted if we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information.
